Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES I: CORRESPONDENCE, 1853-1945
  - INTERNAL
    - PRESIDENT, NEW YORK, AND SAN FRANCISCO OFFICE
      - INCOMING
        - 1918 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - 1919 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - MANAGER AND NEW ALMADEN OFFICE
      - OUTGOING
        - 1864-1867,letterpress (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - 1876-1882,letterpress, New Almaden to New York (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - 1877-1885,letterpress, New Almaden to San Francisco (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - 1888-1892,letterpress (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - INCOMING
        - 1864-Apr. 1865 (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - May-Dec. 1865,from Bond, Randol, etc. (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Aug.-Dec. 1865,from Supt. Nowland (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - 1865,unsigned, New York Office to New Almaden Office (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Jan.-June 1866 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - July-Sept. 1866 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Oct.-Dec. 1866 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Jan.-Mar. 1867 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Apr.-July 1867 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Aug.-Dec. 1867 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Jan.-June 1868 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - July-Dec. 1868 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Jan.-Apr. 1869 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - May-Aug. 1869 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Sept.-Dec. 1869 (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - 1869 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Jan.-Mar. 1870 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Apr.-Dec. 1870 (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - 1871 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - 1872 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - 1873 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - 1874 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - 1877 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - 1878 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - 1879 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - 29 June 1880 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - May-Sept. 1881 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Oct.-Dec. 1881 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - 1882 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - 1883,Surveyor to Manager (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - 1883 (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - 1884 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - 1885 (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - 1886 (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - 1887 (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - 1888 (Box 31, Folder 18)
        - 1889 (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - 1889-1890 (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - 1890 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - 1891 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - 1891-1901 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - 1892 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - 1892,Superintendant to Manager (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - 1893-1894 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - 1908-1909 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - 1910,telegrams (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - 1911 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - 1911,telegrams (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - 1912 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - 1912,telegrams (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - 1913 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - 1913,telegrams (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - 1914 (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - 1914,telegrams (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Jan.-June 1915 (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - July-Aug. 1915 (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Sept.-Dec. 1915 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - 1915,telegrams (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Jan.-July 1916 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Aug.-Dec. 1916 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - 1917 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - 1918 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - 1919 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - 1926 (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - 1927-1928 (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - 1943,re: Ammerman's drafting (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Telegrams, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - SUPERINTENDENT
      - OUTGOING
        - Jan. 1864-Oct. 1866,letterpress (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Oct. 1866-Mar. 1870,letterpress (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - 1880-1883,letterpress (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - 1883-1887,letterpress, Superintendent to San Francisco (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - 1885-1887,letterpress, Superintendent, general letters (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - 1887-1891,letterpress (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - 1891-1895 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - 1896-1898,letterpress (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - 1898-1901,letterpress (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - 1902,letterpress (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - 1902-1909,letterpress, monthly reports (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - 1908-1911,letterpress, letters and telegrams (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - INCOMING
        - 1864 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - 1864 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Sept.-Nov. 1866 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Dec. 1866 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Jan.-Apr. 1867 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - May-Aug. 1867 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Aug.-Dec. 1867 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Jan.-Apr. 1868 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - May-Dec. 1868 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Jan.-June 1869 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - July-Dec. 1869 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - 1870 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - 1881 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Feb.-Aug. 1882 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Sept. 1882 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Oct. 1882 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Nov. 1882 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Dec. 1882 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Jan. 1882 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Feb. -Mar. 1882 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Apr. -June 1882 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - 1883[attached] (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - 1883[attached] (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Dec. 1883 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Jan.-Mar. 1884 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Apr.-June 1884 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - July-Sept. 1884 (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Oct.-Dec. 1884 (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Jan.-Mar. 1885 (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Apr.-June 1885 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - July-Aug. 1885 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Sept.-Dec. 1885 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - 1885,fragments (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Mar.-May 1886 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - June-Sept. 1886 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Oct.-Dec. 1886 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Jan.-Feb. 1887 (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Mar.-Dec. 1887 (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - 1888 (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - 1888[attached] (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - 1889 (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - 1890-1892 (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - 1899 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - 1900 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - 1901 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - 1902 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - 1902-1909(Superintendent to President only) (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - 1903 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - 1904 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - 1905 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - 1906 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - 1907 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- SERIES II: CORPORATE RECORDS, 1864-1927
  - CONFIDENCE GOLD MINES CORPORATION RECORDS, 1919
    - Corporate history (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Resolutions, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Stock records, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Stock records, 1919 and n.d. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - EUREKA COMPANY RECORDS, 1894-1909
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1897 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1899 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1900 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1901 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1902 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1903 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1904 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1905 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1908 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Annual report to the stockholders, 1908-1909 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Business agreements, 1894 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Resolutions, 1908 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - GUADALUPE MINING COMPANY RECORDS, 1888
    - Assessment of property, 1888 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - NEW ALMADEN COMPANY INCORPORATED RECORDS, 1916-1925
    - ADMINISTRATIVE DOCUMENTS
      - Agreements, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Minute book #1, 1915 (Box 41, Volume 1)
      - Minute book #2, 1915 (Box 41, Volume 2)
      - Minutes, 1916-1925 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Notices, 1915-1923 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Report to the State Corporate Commission, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Resolutions, 1919-1922 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Waivers of meeting notification, 1924-1925 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - STOCK MATERIALS
      - Agreement of stock transaction, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Licensees, list of, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Licensees, notice, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - List of stockholders, 1916, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Minute book of stockholders, Mar. 1916 (Box 1)
      - Minutes, stockholder meetings, 1916-1925 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Notices to stockholders, 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Proxies, 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Resolutions of stockholders, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - TAX MATERIALS
      - Assessment, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Returns, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Statements, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Reports to the Stockholders, Quarterly, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - NEW ALMADEN QUICKSILVER MINES CORPORATION RECORDS, 1916-1926
    - ADMINISTRATIVE DOCUMENTS
      - Charter, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Minutes, 1916-1924 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Record book, corporate scrapbook, n.d. (Box 42, Volume 3)
      - Resolutions, 1923-1924 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Statements of engagements, 1916-1917 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Waivers of meeting notification, 1923-1924 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - STOCK MATERIALS
      - Common stock lists, 1918-1925 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Escrow stock, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - List of stockholders, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Notices to stockholders, 1919-1926 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - Preferred stock, 1918-1925 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Proxies, 1919, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - Transfers, common stock, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - TAX MATERIALS
      - Refund claims, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - Returns, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - NEW ALMADEN STORES INCORPORATED RECORDS, 1915-1926
    - ADMINISTRATIVE DOCUMENTS
      - By-laws, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - Certificate of authenticity, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 37)
      - Dissolution, 1925-1926 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - Minutes, 1917-1923 (Box 42, Folder 39)
      - Notices, 1923 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      - Officers, list, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 41)
      - Resolutions, 1917, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - STOCK MATERIALS
      - Proxies, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - TAX MATERIALS
      - Demand, 1920 (Box 42, Folder 44)
      - Reports, 1919 and n.d. (Box 42, Folder 45)
      - Returns, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - QUICKSILVER INVESTMENT COMPANY INCORPORATED RECORDS, 1915-1916
    - ADMINISTRATIVE DOCUMENTS
      - By-laws, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 47)
      - Certificate of incorporation, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 48)
      - Minute book #1, 1915 (Box 42, Volume 4)
    - STOCK MATERIALS
      - Common stock, deposit certificates and installment receipts, 1915 (Box 1)
      - Minute book #1, Apr. 1915-Feb. 1916 (Box 1)
      - Minute book #2, Apr. 1915-Feb. 1916 (Volume 5)
  - QUICKSILVER MINING COMPANY RECORDS, 1864-1923
    - REPORTS TO THE PRESIDENT AND BOARD OF DIRECTORS
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1866 (Box 42, Folder 49)
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1868 (Box 42, Folder 50)
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1869 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1874 (Box 42, Folder 52)
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 53)
      - Engineer's reports, annual, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Foreman's reports, annual, 1908 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1867-1868 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1870 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1871 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1872 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1873 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1874 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1875 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1876 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1877 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1878 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1879 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1880 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1881 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1882 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1883 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1884 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1886 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1887 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1890 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1892 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1894 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1895 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1896 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1897 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Manager's reports, monthly, 1899 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1876 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1876 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1878 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1879 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1880 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, second quarter, 1880 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1881 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, third quarter 1881 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1882 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, second quarter, 1882 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, third quarter, 1882 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1883 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Manager's reports, quarterly, first quarter, 1884 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1865 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1872-1876 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1877-1878 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1879-1882 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1883-1886 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1887 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1887-1892 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1893-1894 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1895-1896 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1896-1897 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1897-1898 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1909-1910 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Manager's reports, annual, 1914-1915 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Manager's reports, annual, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1901 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1905 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1906 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1907 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1908 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Superintendent's reports, monthly, 1909 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Surveyor's reports, monthly, 1899 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Surveyor's reports, monthly, 1900 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - REPORTS TO THE STOCKHOLDERS
      - President's annual report, 1868 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - President's annual report, 1869 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - President's annual report, 1870 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - President's annual report, 1877 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - President's annual report, 1878 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - President's annual report, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - President's annual report, 1881 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - President's annual report, 1882 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - President's annual report, 1885-1886 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - President's annual report, 1889-1890 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - President's annual report, statement of earnings, addenda, 1890 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - President's annual report, 1890-1891 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - President's annual report, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - President's, Secretary's, and Engineer's annual report, [bound together], 1865, 1866, 1868-1875, (printed copies) (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Secretary's report on stockholder meeting, 1866-1882 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Secretary's report on stockholder meeting, 1883-1887 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's report on stockholder meeting, 1888-1891 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Secretary's report on stockholder meeting, 1892, 1895-1896, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Secretary's report on stockholder meeting, 1910-1912 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - ADMINISTRATIVE DOCUMENTS
      - Acts, 1866 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - By-laws, charter, 1864 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - History of Quicksilver Mining Company, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Minutes, 1911-1912 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Minutes, 1912-1915 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Notices, 1877-1913 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Resolutions, 1864-1915 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - STOCK MATERIAL
      - Agreement, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Capital stock, 1917 and n.d. (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Capital stock, certificate, 1882 and n.d. (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Capital stock, 1876-1881 (Box 1)
      - Committee, stockholders, 1914 (Volume 6)
      - Common stock, dividend checks, 1881 (Box 2)
      - Common stock, lists, 1914-1916 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Common stock, share receipts, 1909 (Box 2)
      - Elections of Board of Directors, 1910-1912 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Minutes, noteholders' meetings, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Minutes, stockholders' meetings, 1893-1915 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Noteholders, list, 1913 and n.d. (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Notices to stockholders, 1911-1918 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Outstanding stocks, 1875, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Preferred stock, certificates, 1901-1902 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Preferred stock, index, n.d. (Box 2)
      - Preferred stock, lists, 1914-1916 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Preferred stock, certificates, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Preferred stock, share receipts, 1892-1909 (Box 2)
      - Preferred stock, transfers, 1912-1913 (Box 2)
      - Proxies, 1910-1917 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Stock receipts, 1902 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Stock reports, 1864, 1913, and n.d. (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Stockholders, list, 1912, 1915, and n.d. (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Transfer book, 1909-1915 (Box 3)
      - Transfer, book, 1915-1917 (Box 3)
      - Transfer book, 1915-1917 (Box 4)
      - Transfer receipts, 1879 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Transfer receipts, 1877-1879, and n.d., 3 books (Box 5)
      - Transfer receipts, 1877-1882, 4 books (Box 6)
    - TAX MATERIALS
      - City and county taxes, 1884-1908 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Notices, 1916-1917 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Receipts, 1896-1909 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Report, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Returns, 1894-1917 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - Statements, 1885-1908 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- SERIES III: MINE OPERATIONS AND PRODUCTION, 1850-1960
  - REPORTS TO THE MANAGER, 1865-1955
    - Daily reports, 1878-1879 (Box 49, Volume 7)
    - Daily reports (Box 49, Volume 8)
    - Daily reports, 1881 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Daily reports, 1898 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Daily reports, July-Dec. 1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Daily reports, Jan.-Sept. 1910 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Daily reports, Oct. 1910-Mar. 1911 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Daily reports, Sept.-Dec. 1911 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Daily reports, Jan. 1912 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Daily reports, May-Nov. 1912 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Daily reports, Apr.-Dec. 1915 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Daily reports, 1916 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Daily reports, Jan.-Feb. 1917 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Daily reports, May 1940-June 1941 (Box 51, Folder 5a)
    - Development record, ca. 1924(weekly, below ground) (Box 51, Folder 5b)
      Add
    - Engineer's report, 1865 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Engineer's report, 1866 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Engineer's report, 1867 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Engineer's report, 1889 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Engineer's report, 1892 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Foreman's report, 1866 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Foreman's report, 1874 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Foreman's report, 1875 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Foreman's report, 1876 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Foreman's report, 1877 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1875 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1877 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1878 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1879 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1880 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Mining Captain's reports, 1881 (Box 52, Folder 6a)
    - Quicksilver receipt book, 1864-1865 (Box 52, Folder 6b)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1864-1868 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1870 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1882 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1883 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1884 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1884-1885 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1885-1886 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1886-1887 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1889 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1889-1890 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1891 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1891-1892 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1898 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1900 (monthly) (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1900-1901 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1901-1902 (fiscal year) (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1902-1903 (fiscal year) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1906 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1907 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1908 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1908-1909 (fiscal year) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1909 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1910 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1915-1917, 1919 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1920 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1921-1923 (monthly) (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Surface Foreman's reports, 1890 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Surface Foreman's report, 1883-1890 (Volume 9)